I've been using the Google Pixel 11 Pro
XL for the past week and this is the
most iPhone Android device you can get
and that makes it amazing because from
day-to-day use, not only is this phone
insanely quick, I mean it feels quicker
than any Samsung phone I've used or
really any Apple device I've used, even
though the chip inside the Tent G6 chip,
which is not a 2 nometer chip, it's a 3
nmter chip, isn't anywhere close to the
same power as those other devices. So,
what's even crazier than that, the
upgraded cameras on this phone lead to
some of the best photos I've seen out of
any device. And don't even give me about
night sight because this phone takes
better nightgraphy than any phone I've
used. It literally takes like no time
because Google said that it's a four and
a half times faster nightsight with the
new tent G6 processor. And I was like,
that's BS. It's not BS because when I
was at a club, I took some pictures.
Everything took like 1 second for night
sight. And they always came out better
than my 17 Pro Max. And then at the same
time, all the different AI features with
Rambler being insanely impressive, it
just leads to a phone that just works
really well. They also improved heat
management. This phone does not
overheat. I had it out in the sun where
it was 105° and the screen never dimmed.
And that screen is insanely bright at
3600 nits. I have no problem seeing it
outside. And overall, even though it
might come with a little bit less RAM
than before, this device is actually
quite amazing, especially with how good
the battery life is and charging speed
is on this device. The only qual I
really have with this phone though is
that I wish they updated the GPU cuz if
you wanted to game, this phone is not
for you. Unfortunately, Galaxy devices
with the Snapdragon 8 Elite Gen 5 made
for Galaxy still significantly better as
well as iPhones. But if you don't game
or you just do casual gaming and you
want an Android device that takes photos
insanely easily while also being
insanely good, this device is for you.
and all the light features that just add
to the experience all add up to make
this phone one of my favorite to use,
especially on Android or even compared
to even iPhones as well. Yeah, I got to
say um I'm impressed.